import { Question } from '../interfaces/question';

export const QuestionDDBB: Question[] = [
	{
		id: 1, question: "Who was Google's first female engineer?", answers: {
			correctAnswer: "Marissa Maye", incorrectAnswer1: "Ruchi Sanghvi", incorrectAnswer2: "Jenny Leee", incorrectAnswer3: "Ester Perello"
		}
	},
	{
		id: 2, question: "According to Staista, how many female employees tech jobs worked  at Facebook, Google and Apple in 2020? ", answers: {
			correctAnswer: "23%", incorrectAnswer1: "34%", incorrectAnswer2: "10%", incorrectAnswer3: "12%"
		}
	},
	{
		id: 3, question: "Can you guess the percentage of tech startups that have at least one woman on the board of directors? ", answers: {
			correctAnswer: "37%", incorrectAnswer1: "54%", incorrectAnswer2: "10%", incorrectAnswer3: "22%"
		}
	},
	{
		id: 4, question: "Which startup runs the first international online hackathon for women programmers? ", answers: {
			correctAnswer: "Nuwe", incorrectAnswer1: "Mighty Networks", incorrectAnswer2: "Wompreneur", incorrectAnswer3: "Cisco"
		}
	},
	{
		id: 5, question: "Who is the only foreign lady tech CEO in India? ", answers: {
			correctAnswer: "Valerie Wagoner", incorrectAnswer1: "Jenny Lee", incorrectAnswer2: "Justine Collache", incorrectAnswer3: "Janice Bryant Howroyd"
		}
	},
	{
		id: 6, question: "What's the percentage of tech startups across the world are founded by women ? ", answers: {
			correctAnswer: "20%", incorrectAnswer1: "3%", incorrectAnswer2: "60%", incorrectAnswer3: "15%"
		}
	},
	{
		id: 7, question: "Who was one of the original programmers for the ENIAC computer? ", answers: {
			correctAnswer: "Jean Jennings Bartik", incorrectAnswer1: "Stephanie Hannon", incorrectAnswer2: "Sara Righetti", incorrectAnswer3: "Elizabeth Holmes"
		}
	},
	{
		id: 8, question: "Who is the first developer?", answers: { correctAnswer: "Ada Lovelace", incorrectAnswer1: "Charles Babbage", incorrectAnswer2: "Konrad Zuse", incorrectAnswer3: "Fran Bilas" }
	},
	{
		id: 9, question: "Who was one of the original programmers for the ENIAC computer? ", answers: {
			correctAnswer: "Jean Jennings Bartik", incorrectAnswer1: "Stephanie Hannon", incorrectAnswer2: "Sara Righetti", incorrectAnswer3: "Elizabeth Holmes"
		}
	},
	{
		id: 10, question: "Who is going to win the nuwe Femhack Frontend Group Challenge?", answers: {
			correctAnswer: "Team 12", incorrectAnswer1: "Team 12", incorrectAnswer2: "Team 12", incorrectAnswer3: "Team 12"
		}
	},
];